cashora.com 2017-05-06

# Privacy Policy - Cashora

At Cashora, we understand the value of your privacy and make every possible effort to ensure that all your personal information remains secure at all times.

We hold only a minimal amount of information on each registered member.

To register as a member, we only require an email address and a password. Prior to sending any payments, we will also require relevant account details in order to give you your money.

We only hold information in order to allow users to log into and run their accounts. We will also keep accounts updated with cashback levels. Registered users may update their account details online by following the relevant links from within their account page.

Member usernames and basic related statistics may occasionally be exposed. Examples of this include where a person has followed your referral link, they may see your name; and where a member who was referred to Cashora has a balance under the referral threshold amount, that balance may be visible to the referring member. If you were referred to Cashora this latter fact will be made clear in your account details page, from which you may opt-out of allowing the referrer from being able to see your account balance.

### An Overview

Cashora.com stores, processes and uses your personal details in order to provide you cashback, customer support and various other services. 

In this document, "We" and "us" refers to Cashora.com. "Retailers" refer to online merchants, stores and businesses affiliated with us.

## Information we collect

### Personal Information

When you signup with Cashora, we collect your name and email address. We also capture your IP address for security purposes. Your email address is critical for a seamless communication between you and Cashora.

Your personal information helps us to know your better enabling us to serve you better too.

### Sensitive Details

In order to process your request for a wire transfer, we collect your bank account details such as bank account number and the IFSC code of your bank branch. We also collect and store your mailing address in case you opt for cheque to redeem your cashback.

### Site Usage Details

We also keep a log of your movement on Cashora.com. These details contribute to our research and analysis and help us to enhance our layout, design and user interface. In order, to keep your cashback balance updated, we also keep a track of your clicks to retailer pages. We do not store the details such as your credit/debit card number or any other information that you might provide while making a purchase on any of our affiliated retailer's website. It may also be possible we may want to use your personal information for special means or purpose, not stated in our privacy policy. In this case, we will seek your prior consent before using your personal details.

### Information Sharing

We do not share any of your personal details with any third party unless you may specifically give us your consent to do so. However, we may share your details with retailers in order to validate or track your cashback earnings. We may also need to share your information with organizations that assist us in our various business processes.

We may also be bound to share your information if we are forced to do so by the law, or receive a valid request by a law enforcement or government authority.
